winmasters.com 2016-04-05

# Privacy Policy

****

### Introduction

**winmasters** wants visitors to its website to know that we are just as concerned as you are about the privacy of any personal information that you may choose to provide us ("Personal Information").

Personal Information is any information about you and may include your name and address, date of birth, payment card details, details of betting transactions and account transfers and any other information you may wish to provide. **winmasters** is endeavoring to ensure that our business practices that involve the use of your Personal Information are compliant with privacy regulations in the countries where we operate. Accordingly, in this policy document (the "Privacy Policy"), **winmasters** wants not only to advise you of your privacy rights but also explain how we intend to respect them.

Any reference to " **winmasters** " within this Privacy Policy includes WM Interactive Limited and all or any of its direct or indirect subsidiary undertakings, joint venture partners, and their related companies wherever located in the world as may exist from time to time.

### How is your Personal Information collected by our website?

Personal Information may be submitted on our website in two areas:

#### 1.     Public Area

If you do provide your name and address on the public area of this website in order to request information about our products and services, you may voluntarily provide additional personal information. You will be asked to provide your personal information in this area for the purposes of registering with **winmasters** and opening an account with us.

#### 2.     Private Area

If you are already one of our customers and have opened an account with us, you must use a password to enter the **winmasters** website. A "session cookie" is used to enable you to leave and re-enter our website without re-entering your password. Our web server will record the pages you visit within our website.

To ensure a good quality of service we may monitor and record any communication you have with us whether in writing, by phone or by electronic mail. E-mail is not encrypted to / from either the public or private areas of this website. **winmasters** recommends that with the exception of your name and username you do not send us Personal Information by e-mail. Any information which you transmit to us is transmitted at your own risk.

## How we use Cookies on our Site and what Information we collect

**winmasters** uses ‘cookies’ in order to provide you with a better experience.

## How your Personal Information will be used?

**winmasters** will process your Personal Information in order to allow you access and make use of our website, to allow you to participate in the services offered, to administer your account, to maintain our accounts and records, to monitor website usage levels and the quality of the service we provide and to inform you, from time to time, about products and services that we consider may interest you and for related purposes. If you do not wish to receive future marketing, promotional or sales material from **winmasters** , you may notify us that no further material be sent to you. Our contact details are located in the 'Contact Us' pages of our website. **winmasters** will as soon as reasonably practicable after receiving your request, remove your contact details from our marketing database.

**winmasters** will also retain such information and may analyze it in order to investigate any actual or suspected criminal activity or, in respect of any event featured on our website, any threat to the integrity of that event and/or breaches of the rules of that event as laid down by the relevant governing (including sporting) bodies. All rights in the manner of recording your Personal Information held by **winmasters** (including copyright and database rights) are and shall remain its property.

Telephone calls and betting data relating to users will be recorded and may be actively monitored for which purposes all users hereby consent.

### To whom and where personal information may be disclosed?

Your Personal Information may, for the purposes described above, be transferred or disclosed to **winmasters** or, subject to appropriate agreement to third parties, for the processing of that Personal Information on our behalf. The **winmasters** may, from time to time, retain third parties to process your Personal Information for the purposes listed above and such processing will be governed by a contract in the form required by law.

Where required by law, your Personal Information may also be disclosed to an applicable governmental, regulatory, sporting or enforcement authority. Additionally, in circumstances where we deem it appropriate, your Personal Information may be disclosed to any regulatory authority (whether at the request of such authority or otherwise) which has issued **winmasters** with a gambling operating license.

In connection with the above purposes it may be necessary, or a legal requirement, for **winmasters** to disclose information to entities located in countries in accordance with appropriate technical and organizational security measures. By agreeing to this policy, by use of the **winmasters** site or otherwise, you agree that **winmasters** may store and use historical data relating to you and your account(s) for the purposes outlined in this policy.

### Consent

By providing your Personal Information and registering with us or logging on with us when you enter our website, you explicitly consent to the **winmasters** processing and disclosing your Personal Information for the purposes, and otherwise in the manner set out in this policy, or as otherwise provided in accordance with the Terms and Conditions. If you wish to qualify, vary, modify or limit your consent in relation to marketing communications or in circumstances where any processing of your data is likely to cause damage or distress or such other circumstances as the law allows then you may do so by notifying us in writing. Our contact details are located in the 'Contact Us' pages of our website.

### General information

You may at any time request a copy of your Personal Information held by **winmasters** in accordance with subject access rules in the Data Protection Act 2001 (Malta).

**winmasters** reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy including altering the purposes for which it processes your Personal Information. In the event that **winmasters** considers it appropriate to make any such change, the Privacy Policy will be updated and posted on our site. Your continued use of the site will constitute acceptance of those changes.

For full details about **winmasters** , where we operate, or for a copy of your Personal Information or any other queries you may have about our Privacy Policy, please contact us.

**winmasters** website including those optimized for mobile and tablet devices use cookies and similar technologies to manage login sessions, provide personalized web pages and to tailor advertising and other content to reflect your specific needs and interests. By using **winmasters** website you agree to the use of cookies and similar technologies for the purposes we describe in this policy.

## What is a web cookie?

Cookies are text files containing a small amount of information that are downloaded to your device when you visit a website. They are generally used by most websites to improve your online experience and to ensure that content and functions are delivered and used more effectively.

Cookies perform various different functions. For example, some cookies are downloaded to your device temporarily for the period that you browse a particular website; these cookies might allow you to navigate between pages more efficiently or enable websites to remember the preferences you select. Other cookies can be used to help websites remember you as a returning visitor or ensure the online adverts you receive are more relevant to your specific needs and interests

You can amend your browser settings to block some or all cookies. To do this, follow the instructions provided by your browser manufacturer. However, if you block cookies from **winmasters** website some or all the website’s functions may not perform as intended. For example, you may not actually be able to place any bets.

The types of cookies **winmasters** use are:

**Essential Cookies**

‘Essential Cookies are cookies which are necessary in order for a website to function correctly; they enable you to navigate a website and allow you to perform specific functions, such as accessing secure areas, placing bets, depositing funds and managing your account. Without these cookies, it would not be possible to provide specific online services and functions.

**We use Essential Cookies to…**

  * Remember information you've entered on order forms when you navigate to different pages in a single web browser session
  * Maintain your betslip selections as you navigate around the site
  * Identify you as being logged into **winmasters**.com
  * Make sure we deliver the correct site features for your geographic location

**Cookies we have defined as Essential Cookies will not be used to…**

  * Gather information that could be used to advertise products or services to you
  * Remember your preferences or username beyond your current visit

Some examples of essential cookies that **winmasters** sets:

\- TainToken – The token that is used by Tain to identify users of the site.   
\- WMToken – The token that is used to verify logins from another device.   
\- userInfo - If a user is logged in, it contains all data regarding the user: register date, name, forename, balances, favorite language and currency

**Performance Cookies**

These cookies collect information about how visitors use a website, for instance which pages they go to most often and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. It is only used to improve a website’s performance.

**We use performance cookies to…**

  * Provide statistics on how our website is used
  * See how effective our promotions are
  * Collect statistics on which markets customers are betting on
  * Help us improve the website by measuring any errors that occur
  * Test different designs of our website
  * Identify your browser or device you are using to access the site

**Cookies we have defined as 'Performance' cookies will not be used to…**

  * Gather information that could be used to advertise products or services to you on other websites
  * Remember your preferences or username beyond your current visit
  * Store personal information such as email address or name
  * Target promotions to you on any other website
  * Allow third parties to use the cookies for any purpose other than those listed above

Example of performance cookies that **winmasters** sets:

\- _ga - Google Analytics   
\- com.silverpop.iMAWebCookie - Web and Behavioral Visitor Tracking Whitepapers

Please be aware that opting out of our performance cookies may mean some useful information such as **winmasters** contact details are not available to you, however, if you wish to opt out of any of the web analytics that **winmasters** use, please use the links below:

**Silverpop**

http://www.silverpop.com/About/Trust--Privacy/Privacy-Policy-Legal/Privacy-Policy/

**Google Analytics**

http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout

**Functionality Cookies**

These cookies allow the website to remember choices you make, such as your user name, language, or the region you are in, and provide enhanced, personalized features. For instance, a website may be able to provide you with local weather reports or traffic news by using cookies to store information about the region in which you are located. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customize. They may also be used to provide services you have requested such as watching a video or commenting on a blog. The information these cookies collect may be anonymized and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.

**We use 'Functionality' cookies to…**

  * Remember settings you've applied such as layout, preferences, colors and showing/ hiding features
  * Remember that you’ve seen certain content
  * Provide proactive live chat sessions to offer you support
  * Share information with partners to provide a service on our website. The information shared is only to be used to provide the service, product or function and not for any other purpose
  * Show recent markets that you have viewed

**Cookies defined as 'Functionality' will not be used to…**

  * Target you with adverts on other websites
  * Allow third parties to use the cookies for any purpose other than those listed above

Examples of functionality cookies that **winmasters** sets:

**Local Storage cookies**

\- BetSlipStorage - Betslip data such as match id’s and odds selections.   
\- OddsBetFormat - Odds format decimal, fractional, American  
\- SaveBonusService - Actual active bonus   
\- SportsFavorites - Sports favorite leagues   
\- FilterSettings - Sports filter options   
\- SiteLanguage - The current site language

**Targeting Cookies**

These cookies are used to deliver content, such as adverts, that are more relevant to you and your interests. They may also be used to limit the number of times you see an advert or measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. These tend to be set by third party advertising agencies with **winmasters** permission, and may share information about websites that you have visited with other organizations, such as advertisers.

**We use 'Targeting' cookies to…**

  * Tailor content to customers on sister sites based on whether you are logged in or not on the main **winmasters** site
  * Provide promotions to customers who have registered but not funded their accounts
  * Provide cross-product promotions to customers based on what markets you have viewed or the value of the bets you have placed

Examples of Targeting cookies that winmasters sets:

saveBonus – The bonus code that is applied when registering.
